Register of the Socialist Workers Party Records, 1928-1990
Hoover Institution Archives
- GEOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1928-1989. (Box No. 23-45, 58-62)
  - Ireland (Box 41.)
    - General
      - 1941-1942 (Folder 1)
      - 1943-1944 (Folder 2)
      - 1945-1948 (Folder 3)
      - 1969 (Folder 4)
      - 1985 (Box 62., Folder 5)
    - Revolutionary Socialist Party. Workers' Republic. Vol. 1 no. 1 (1947 May-June) (Box 41., Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1941 (Folder 6)
  - Israel, 1982-1983 (Box 62., Folder 6)
  - Italy (Box 41.)
    - General
      - 1937 (Folder 7)
      - 1943 (Folder 8)
      - 1944 (Folder 9)
      - 1945
        - January-June (Folder 10)
        - July-December (Folder 11)
      - 1946 (Folder 12)
      - 1947-1970 (Folder 13)
    - Partito Operaio Comunista
      - Bollettino Interno. Unnumbered (1945?), no. 2 (1945), no. 3 (1945), supplement (1945), no. 8 (1947 September 3) (Folder 14)
      - Militante. No. 1 (1944 October 30) (Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous publications, 1945 (Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1943-1944 (Folder 17)
  - Jamaica, 1947-1963 (Folder 18)
  - Japan
    - General
      - 1948-1949 (Folder 19)
      - 1950-1956 (Folder 20)
      - 1959 (Folder 21)
      - 1960
        - February-June (Folder 22)
        - July (Folder 23)
        - August-November (Box 42., Folder 1)
      - 1961-1962 (Folder 2)
      - 1963-1964 (Folder 3)
      - 1966-1967 (Folder 4)
      - 1968 (Folder 5)
      - 1969-1970 (Folder 6)
    - Kakumeiteki Kyosanshugisha Domei [Revolutionary Communist League]
      - Sekai Kakumei [World Revolution]. No. 98 (1962 November 10), no. 99 (November 25), no. 103 (1963 August 25) (Folder 7)
      - Zenshin. 1963 (Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1962-1964 (Folder 9)
  - Korea, 1946 (Folder 10)
  - Latin America (general), 1935-1973 (Folder 11)
  - Malaya, 1945 (Folder 12)
  - Mexico. Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, and material re Fourth International relations with Diego Rivera
    - General
      - 1938 (Folder 13)
      - 1939
        - January-February (Folder 14)
        - March-August (Folder 15)
      - 1940 (Folder 16)
      - 1941 (Folder 17)
      - 1942-1943 (Folder 18)
      - 1944 (Folder 19)
      - 1945 (Folder 20)
      - 1946 (Folder 21)
      - 1947 (Folder 22)
      - 1948-1949 (Folder 23)
      - 1950-1952 (Folder 24)
      - 1954-1955 (Folder 25)
      - 1966-1967 (Folder 26)
      - 1982 (Box 62., Folder 7)
      - 1983 (Folder 8)
      - 1984 (Folder 9)
    - Liga Comunista Internacionalista. Boletín Interno. No. 2 (1938) (Box 43., Folder 1)
    - Liga Socialista. Boletín Interno. Unnumbered (1974 July) (Folder 2)
    - Partido Revolucionario de los Trabajadores (Box 62.)
      - Boletín Interno de Discusión e Información. No. 74 (1986 May), no. 75 (October), no. 76 (November), no. 77 (November) (Folder 10)
      - Documentos de Discusión Preparatoria del V Congreso del PRT. No. 1 (1987 June), no. 2 (June), no. 3 (June), no. 4 (July), no. 5 (July) (Folder 11)
  - Netherlands (Box 43.)
    - General
      - 1933-1942 (Folder 3)
      - 1945 (Folder 4)
      - 1946 (Folder 5)
      - 1947 (Folder 6)
      - 1948-1949 (Folder 7)
    - Revolutionnair Communistische Partij. Circulated internal documents
      - 1945 (Folder 8)
      - 1946 (Folder 9)
      - 1947 (Folder 10)
  - New Zealand
    - General
      - 1967 (Folder 11)
      - 1968 (Folder 12)
      - 1969 (Folder 13)
      - 1970-1972 (Folder 14)
      - 1983 (Box 62., Folder 12)
    - Socialist Action League
      - Discussion Bulletin. Vol. 11 no. 1 (1985 December), no. 2 (December) (Folder 13)
      - Information Bulletin. No. 1 (1985 October), no. 2 (November), no. 3 (December), no. 4 (December), no. 5 (December), no. 6 (December) (Folder 14)
      - Minutes, 1970 (Box 43., Folder 15)
      - Organiser. Vol. 1 no. 1 (1970 September 21), no. 4 (1972 February) (Folder 16)
      - Socialist Action
        - 1970. Vol. 2 no. 2 (February 20), no. 3 (March 6) (Folder 17)
        - 1983. Vol. 15 no. 13 (July 15) (Box 62., Folder 15)
      - Towards a Workers' and Farmers' Government in New Zealand: Documents of the Socialist Action League, 1982-1986, 1986 (Folder 16)
      - Newspaper articles, 1982-1983 (Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous issuances, 1969-1970 (Box 43., Folder 18)
    - Socialist Union. Declaration, 1954 (Folder 19)
    - Young Socialists. Information Bulletin. No. 1 (1986 May), no. 2 (May), no. 1 [sic] (May) (Box 62., Folder 18)
  - Nigeria, 1945-1959 (Box 43., Folder 20)
  - Norway, 1946 (Folder 21)
  - Palestine
    - General
      - 1945 (Folder 22)
      - 1946 (Folder 23)
      - 1947-1949 (Folder 24)
    - Printed article, 1968 (Folder 25)
  - Panama
    - 1937 (Folder 26)
    - 1979 (Box 62., Folder 19)
  - Peru (Box 43.)
    - 1945 (Folder 27)
    - 1946 (Folder 28)
    - 1947-1948 (Folder 29)
    - 1960-1969 (Folder 30)
    - 1977 (Box 62., Folder 20)
  - Philippines, 1946 (Box 43., Folder 31)
  - Poland
    - General, 1943-1946 (Folder 32)
    - Liga Robotników Polskich. Pamphlet. T. Zygmunt Konarski, Proletarjat Zdradzony: Dzieje Ruchu Rewolucyjnego, 1938 (Folder 33)
  - Puerto Rico, 1940-1968 (Folder 34)
  - Scandinavia (general), 1941-1945 (Folder 35)
  - South Africa (Box 44.)
    - General
      - 1937-1938 (Folder 1)
      - 1939 (Folder 2)
      - 1941-1944 (Folder 3)
      - 1945-1946 (Folder 4)
      - 1947-1948 (Folder 5)
      - 1961 (Folder 6)
      - 1963-1964 (Folder 7)
      - 1965 (Folder 8)
      - 1966-1968 (Folder 9)
    - Alexander Defense Committee. Pamphlets, 1965-1966 (Folder 10)
    - Fourth International Organisation. Circulated internal documents, ca. 1945 (Folder 11)
    - Propaganda Group for a Fourth International. Leaflets and flyers, 1937 (Folder 12)
    - Socialist Workers League. Socialist Action. Vol. 1 no. 1 (1939 June), no. 2 (July) (Folder 13)
    - Workers' Party of South Africa. Circulated internal document, 1948 (Folder 14)
  - Spain. Includes material re Spaniards in exile, especially in Mexico
    - General
      - 1941 (Folder 15)
      - 1942 (Folder 16)
      - 1943 (Folder 17)
      - 1944 (Folder 18)
      - 1945 (Folder 19)
      - 1946 (Folder 20)
      - 1950-1951 (Folder 21)
    - Grupo Comunista-Internacionalista. Boletín de Discusión. No. 25 (1949 January) (Folder 22)
    - Izquierda Communista Española. Boletín Interior. No. 6 (1933 December 28) (Folder 23)
  - Sri Lanka
    - General
      - 1942-1949 (Folder 24)
      - 1950-1954 (Folder 25)
      - 1956-1959 (Folder 26)
      - 1960 (Folder 27)
      - 1961-1965 (Folder 28)
    - Ceylon Socialist Students Association. Afro-Asian Socialist Review. No. 2 (1962 April) (Box 45., Folder 1)
    - Lanka Sama Samaja Party
      - Internal Bulletin. Unnumbered (1947), no. 1 (1950), no. 2 (1950), unnumbered (1954 March) (Folder 2)
      - Samasamajist. Vol. 1 no. 1 (1944 November), unnumbered (1945 January), unnumbered (April-May); vol. 24 no. 17 (1960 March 4), no. 20 (April 1), no. 22 (April 22), no. 23 (April 29), no. 24 (May 6), no. 25 (May 20) (Folder 3)
      - Circulated internal documents, 1945-1947 (Folder 4)
  - Sweden
    - 1949 (Folder 5)
    - 1988 (Box 62., Folder 21)
  - Switzerland (Box 45.)
    - General, 1945-1946 (Folder 6)
    - Linke Opposition. Mitteilungen. No. 1 (1931 August), no. 2 (late August) (Folder 7)
  - Thailand, 1948 (Folder 8)
  - Trinidad, 1945-1946 (Folder 9)
  - United States (Box 62.)
    - Fourth Internationalist Tendency. Platform, 1984; Internal Information Bulletin(1984 September) (Folder 22)
    - Socialist Action. Information Bulletin. Vol. 1 no. 1 (1984 January), no. 2 (February), no. 3 (April, 2 volumes), no. 4 (May) (Folder 23)
  - Uruguay (Box 45.)
    - 1940-1945 (Folder 10)
    - 1946-1947 (Folder 11)
    - 1954-1961 (Folder 12)
  - Vietnam, 1947-1950 (Folder 13)
  - Yugoslavia, 1949-1961 (Folder 14)
  - Zaire, 1966 (Folder 15)
- INTERNATIONAL ASSIGNMENTS FILE, 1962-1987. (Box No. 45-46, 63)
  Reports to the Socialist Workers Party by party representatives with international assignments, and correspondence between the party and these representatives. Arranged alphabetically by name of representative.
  - Benson, John, 1977 (Europe) (Box 63., Folder 1)
  - Benson, John, and Sam Anderson, 1972-1976 (Europe) (Box 45., Folder 16)
  - Buch, Peter, 1971 (Algeria, Europe) (Folder 17)
  - Camejo, Peter
    - 1969-1976 (Latin America, Europe) (Folder 18)
    - 1979 (Latin America) (Box 63., Folder 2)
  - Garza, Richard, 1971 (Mexico) (Box 45., Folder 19)
  - Halstead, Fred, 1972-1973 (Latin America) (Folder 20)
  - Hansen, Joseph
    - 1962-1975 (Latin America, Europe) (Folder 21)
    - 1978 (Latin America) (Box 63., Folder 3)
  - Hillman, Terry, 1972 (Spain) (Box 45., Folder 22)
  - Horowitz, Gus
    - 1971-1973 (India, Sri Lanka, Middle East) (Folder 23)
    - 1974 (India, Europe) (Folder 24)
  - Horowitz, Gus, and Becky Finch (Box 46.)
    - 1975 (Europe, India) (Folder 1)
    - 1976
      - January-May (Europe) (Folder 2)
      - June-December (Europe, Middle East) (Folder 3)
    - 1977-1978 (Europe, Middle East, Hong Kong, Mexico) (Box 63., Folder 4)
  - Jenness, Doug, 1980 (Great Britain) (Folder 5)
  - Lamont, Susan, 1973 (Europe) (Box 46., Folder 4)
  - Manuel, Sam, 1987 (Guyana) (Box 63., Folder 6)
  - Riddell, John, 1972-1973 (Europe, Peru, Mexico) (Box 46., Folder 5)
  - Shaw, Ed
    - 1972-1973 (Latin America) (Folder 6)
    - 1974-1976 (Latin America, Spain, Portugal) (Folder 7)
    - 1977 (Colombia) (Box 63., Folder 7)
  - Sheppard, Barry, 1969-1976 (Europe, Japan, India) (Box 46., Folder 8)
  - Sheppard, Barry, and Caroline Lund (Box 63.)
    - 1977 (Europe, Latin America) (Folder 8)
    - 1978 (Europe) (Folder 9)
    - 1979 (Europe) (Folder 10)
  - Steele, John, 1970 (Europe) (Box 46., Folder 9)
  - Stone, Betsey, 1976 (India) (Folder 10)
  - Styron, Dan, 1973 (Europe) (Folder 11)
  - Thomas, Tony, 1973 (Martinique) (Folder 12)
  - Waters, Mary-Alice, 1966 (Europe) (Folder 13)
  - Zimmermann, Matilde, 1973 (Italy) (Folder 14)
- BARNES/WATERS FILE, 1964-1990. (Box No. 47-51, 63-74)
  Papers of Jack Barnes and Mary-Alice Waters as Socialist Workers Party representatives in interactions with the Fourth International, including correspondence, notes, reports, agenda, minutes, declarations, resolutions, appeals, theses, drafts and preparatory material. Consists largely of material documenting meetings of international bodies of the Fourth International. Arranged chronologically.
  - 1964 (Box 47.)
    - General. Includes material on the United States (Robertson group), and the International Marxist Revolutionary Tendency (Folder 1)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, May (Folder 2)
  - 1965. Includes material on the International Marxist Revolutionary Tendency (Folder 3)
  - 1966
    - General. Includes material on Cuba and China (Folder 4)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, July (Folder 5)
  - 1967. Includes material on Great Britain (Folder 6)
  - 1968
    - General. Includes material on France (Folder 7)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, January (Folder 8)
  - 1969
    - General. Includes material on Great Britain (Folder 9)
    - World Congress (9th), April 12-18
      - Minutes (Folder 10)
      - Summary of proceedings (Folder 11)
      - Draft resolutions (Folder 12)
      - Final documents (Folder 13)
      - World Revolution resolution. Notes on discussions (Folder 14)
      - Chinese Cultural Revolution resolution. Notes on discussions (Folder 15)
      - Latin American resolution. Notes on discussions (Folder 16)
      - Miscellany (Folder 17)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, April 20 (Folder 18)
    - United Secretariat meeting, April 20 (Folder 19)
    - Post-World Congress informal talks, April (Folder 20)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 17-18 (Folder 21)
    - United Secretariat meeting, June 14-15 (Folder 22)
  - 1970. Includes material on Great Britain, Czechoslovakia, China, and the anti-Vietnam War movement (Folder 23)
  - 1971
    - General. Includes material on Bolivia and Chile (Folder 24)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 23-24 (Folder 25)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 20-21 (Folder 26)
    - United Secretariat meeting, April 17-18 (Folder 27)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 29-November 1 (Folder 28)
  - 1972 (Box 48.)
    - General. Includes material on Canada, the Antilles, Bolivia, Chile, Argentina, Great Britain, Sweden, Czechoslovakia, Yugoslavia, Angola, Hong Kong, Australia, Arab countries, and the anti-Vietnam War movement
      - January-May (Folder 1)
      - June-December (Folder 2)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 4-5 (Folder 3)
    - United Secretariat meeting, April 16-17 (Folder 4)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 20-21 (Folder 5)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 23-25 (Folder 6)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 28-29 (Folder 7)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, December 2-6 (Folder 8)
  - 1973
    - General. Includes material on Bolivia, Chile, Argentina, Great Britain, France, the United States (Internationalist Tendency), and the Leninist-Trotskyist Faction and International Majority Tendency within the Fourth International (Folder 9)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 20 (Folder 10)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 17-19 (Folder 11)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 23-26 (Folder 12)
  - 1974
    - General. Includes material on Argentina, France, Hong Kong, and the United States (Internationalist Tendency) (Folder 13)
    - World Congress (10th), February
      - Minutes (Folder 14)
      - World Political Situation resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 15)
      - Bolivia resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 16)
      - Argentina resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 17)
      - Armed Struggle in Latin America resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 18)
      - Europe resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 19)
      - Mandates material (re accreditation of participants and votes allotted) (Box 49., Folder 1)
      - Statements and declarations (Folder 2)
      - Internal reports on work of Congress (Folder 3)
      - Press reports (Folder 4)
    - United Secretariat meeting, April 20-21 (Folder 5)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 29-30 (Folder 6)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 7-8 (Folder 7)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 12-13 (Folder 8)
    - United Secretariat meeting, November 16-17 (Folder 9)
    - United Secretariat meeting, December 17 (Folder 10)
  - 1975
    - General. Includes material on France (Organisation Communiste Internationaliste) (Folder 11)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 24 (Folder 12)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, January 27-30
      - Minutes (Folder 13)
      - Argentina resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 14)
      - Economic Situation resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Box 50., Folder 1)
      - International Control Commission report (re Internationalist Tendency [United States]) (Folder 2)
      - International Control Commission report annexes (Folder 3)
      - Miscellany (Folder 4)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 15-16 (Folder 5)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 31-June 1 (Folder 6)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 1-2 (Folder 7)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 4-5 (Folder 8)
    - United Secretariat meeting, November 23-24 (Folder 9)
    - United Secretariat meeting, December 22-23 (Folder 10)
  - 1976
    - General. Includes material on Mexico, Colombia, Argentina, Great Britain, France, Spain, Portugal, Greece, South Africa, China, Japan, political prisoners in Eastern Europe, the International Arab Commission, the Bolshevik Tendency within the Fourth International, and the Organizing Committee for the Reconstruction of the Fourth International
      - February-September (Folder 11)
      - October-November (Folder 12)
      - December (Folder 13)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 24-25 (Folder 14)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, February
      - General. Includes draft resolutions on Portugal and Angola (Folder 15)
      - Voting record (Folder 16)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 13-14 (Folder 17)
    - United Secretariat meeting, April 24-25 (Folder 18)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 22-23 (Box 51., Folder 1)
    - United Secretariat meeting, July 3-4 (Folder 2)
    - United Secretariat meeting, August 2 (Folder 3)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 16-17 (Folder 4)
    - United Secretariat meeting, November 13-14 (Folder 5)
    - United Secretariat meeting, December 20-21 (Folder 6)
  - 1977. Includes material on Costa Rica (Fausto Amador case), Portugal, and the Bolshevik Tendency within the Fourth International (Box 63., Folder 11)
  - 1978
    - General. Includes material on Colombia, France, and Lebanon (Folder 12)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 27-19 (Folder 13)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 31-April 2 (Folder 14)
    - United Secretariat meeting, July 4-6 (Folder 15)
    - United Secretariat meeting, November 6-9 (Folder 16)
  - 1979
    - General. Includes material on Nicaragua, Argentina, Great Britain, France, Spain, Japan, the Bolshevik Faction and the Leninist-Trotskyist Tendency within the Fourth International, and the Organizing Committee for the Reconstruction of the Fourth International
      - February-October (Folder 17)
      - November-December (Folder 18)
    - United Secretariat meeting, February 22-24 (Folder 19)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 31-April 4 (Folder 20)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 26-30 (Box 64., Folder 1)
    - United Secretariat meeting, July 2-5
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Organizing Committee for the Reconstruction of the Fourth International discussion documents (Folder 3-4)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 29-October 3 (Folder 5)
    - World Congress (11th), November
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Notes (Folder 7)
      - Manifesto (Folder 8)
      - Europe resolution. Draft (Folder 9)
      - Latin America resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 10-12)
      - Political resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 13)
      - Political resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Box 65., Folder 1-2)
      - Women's Liberation resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 3)
      - Evaluations (Folder 4)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, November 18 (Folder 5)
  - 1980
    - General. Includes material on the Parity Committee for the Reorganisation (Reconstruction) of the Fourth International
      - February-August (Folder 6)
      - October-December (Folder 7)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 26-29 (Folder 8)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 27-30 (Folder 9)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 30-June 1 (Folder 10)
    - United Secretariat meeting, July 18-21 (Folder 11)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 25-28 (Folder 12)
    - United Secretariat meeting, November 28-December 1 (Folder 13)
  - 1981
    - General. Includes material on Cuba, Great Britain, France, Spain, Poland, South Africa, Turkey/Kurdistan, Iran, China, the United States (lawsuit against the Federal Bureau of Investigation), and the Fourth International (International Committee)
      - January-June (Folder 14)
      - July-October (Folder 15)
      - November-December (Folder 16)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 30-February 1 (Folder 17)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 26-29 (Folder 18)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, May 7-14
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Afghanistan resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Box 66., Folder 1)
      - Cuba resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 2)
      - Poland resolution. Drafts (Folder 3)
      - World Situation resolution. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 4-6)
      - Other resolutions. Drafts and discussion documents (Folder 7)
    - United Secretariat meeting, June 29-30 (Folder 8)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 9-11 (Folder 9)
    - United Secretariat meeting, November 12 (Folder 10)
  - 1982
    - General. Includes material on Ireland, France, Poland, Israel, Iran, the United States (Socialist Workers Party relations with the Fourth International), and the International Centre of Reconstruction of the Fourth International (Folder 11)
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 7-10 (Folder 12)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 11-14 (Folder 13)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 21-22 (Box 67., Folder 1)
    - International Executive Committee plenum, May 22-30
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Minutes (Folder 3)
      - Notes (Folder 4)
      - Central America and Caribbean discussions. Reports and declaration (Folder 5)
      - Industrial Turn discussions. Report, questionnaire and memoranda (Folder 6)
      - Iran discussions. Draft resolutions and discussion documents (Folder 7)
      - Israel discussions. Draft resolution and discussion documents (Folder 8)
      - Malvinas War discussions. Draft declarations (Folder 9)
      - Militarism discussions. Draft resolution and discussion documents (Folder 10)
      - Sri Lanka discussions. Draft resolutions and discussion documents (Folder 11)
      - United States discussions (re Socialist Workers Party). Statements and discussion documents (Folder 12)
      - Other discussions. Reports, draft resolutions, and discussion documents (Folder 13)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 30 (Folder 14)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 2-3 (Folder 15)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 6-10 (Folder 16)
  - 1983
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 24-27 (Folder 17)
    - United Secretariat meeting, March 12-14 (Folder 18)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 27-30
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Building the International report. Draft (Folder 20)
      - World Situation report. Draft (Folder 21)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 7-8 (Box 68., Folder 1)
    - United Secretariat meeting, October 20-24
      - General (Folder 2)
      - United States discussions (re Socialist Workers Party). Draft resolutions and discussion documents (Folder 3)
  - 1984
    - United Secretariat meeting, January 26-29 (Folder 4)
    - European Political Bureaus meeting, February-March (Folder 5)
    - United Secretariat meeting, May 10-14
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Socialist Workers Party motions and countermotions (Folder 7)
      - East discussions (re Soviet Union, Eastern Europe, China). Draft resolutions and discussion documents (Folder 8)
      - Great Britain discussions. Draft resolutions and discussion documents (Folder 9)
      - United States Elections discussions. Draft resolutions and discussion documents (Folder 10)
      - United States Splits (of Fourth Internationalist Tendency and Socialist Action from Socialist Workers Party) discussions. Draft resolutions and discussion documents (Folder 11)
    - United Secretariat meeting, September 6-9 (Folder 12)
    - Latin American Political Bureaus meeting, September (Folder 13)
    - United Secretariat meeting, November 8-11 (Box 69.)
      - General (Folder 1-2)
      - Cuba discussions. Draft amendments (Folder 3)
      - Sri Lanka discussions. Report (Folder 4)
  - 1985
    - International Executive Committee plenum, January 26-27
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Brazil discussions. Background printed articles (Folder 6)
    - World Congress Faction meeting, January 31 (Folder 7)
    - World Congress (12th), January-February
      - Pre-Congress preparatory reports (Folder 8)
      - Appeal to the delegates (by certain members of the International Executive Committee) (Folder 9)